#### Contact

lsxmasondo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ lungelomasondo (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Full-Stack Development Web Development Digital Marketing

### Certifications

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

# Lungelo Masondo

Microsoft AppFactory Intern at Nebula Johannesburg

## Summary

I am currently a software developer intern at Microsoft SA and Nebula. The technical, conceptual and leadership skills I have acquired in the last few years make me a good fit in any innovation driven team. My experience in sales has equipped me with the ability to leverage my knowledge of product and services and directly translate it into sales. I have a passion for solving problems and adding value; I have always sought to push my limits in this regard to ensure the work I produce matters to its users.

## Experience

Nebula

Microsoft AppFactory Intern September 2020 - Present (2 months)

Pretoria, Gauteng, South Africa

Intern Software Engineer with a focus on developing cloud solutions

Di-Monate Foods
Full-Stack Web Developer
July 2020 - Present (4 months)
Kempton Park, Gauteng, South Africa

Web Developer for a small business seeking to expand its online presence. www.dimonatefoods.co.za

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit
Web Content Manager
April 2019 - May 2019 (2 months)

Vereeniging, Gauteng, South Africa

BodyFlo Family Gym
Sales Consultant
September 2015 - February 2017 (1 year 6 months)
Kempton Park, Gauteng, South Africa

Responsible for acquiring new clients

## Education

North-West University / Noordwes-Universiteit

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2017 - 2020)